// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Two objects attract each other by garavitational force F.if mass of one object is doubled but the distance between them reamins unchanged , the gravitational force between these objects will be",
    answer: "2F",
    options: [
      "F/2",
      "F",
      "2F",
      "4F"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the value of G(Universal Gravitational Constant)?",
    answer: "6.67×10⁻¹¹N",
    options: [
      "4.22×²²N",
      "6.67×10⁻¹¹N",
      "3×10N",
      "None of these",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The atmosphere is held to the Earth by",
    answer: "gravity",
    options: [
      "gravity",
      "wind",
      "clouds",
      "earth's magnetic field",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The value of acceleration due to gravity(g) on the surface of te Earth is",
    answer: "9.8m/s²",
    options: [
      "9.8cm/s²",
      "9.8km/s²",
      "9.8cm/s",
      "9.8m/s²"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The value of 'g' at the pole is",
    answer: "greater than the value at the equator",
    options: [
      "greater than the value at the equator",
      "less than the value at the equator",
      "equal to the value at the equator",
      "none of these",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "A heavy stone falls",
    answer: "with the same acceleration as the light stone falls",
    options: [
      "faster than a light stone",
      "slower than a ligth stone",
      "with the same acceleration as the light stone falls",
      "none of these",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "If the weigth of a person on the surface of te Earth is 600N, What will be its weigth on the surface of the Moon",
    answer: "100N",
    options: [
      "100kg",
      "600N",
      "1000kg",
      "100N",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "When a body is thrown up, the force of gravity is",
    answer: "in the downward direction",
    options: [
      "in the downward direction",
      "in horizontal direction",
      "in the upward direction",
      "zero",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Mass is a ________ quantity and weight is a _________ quantity.",
    answer: "scalar,vector",
    options: [
      "vector,vector",
      "vector,scalar",
      "scalar,vector",
      "scalar,scalar",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The motion of moon around the earth is due to the________force.",
    answer: "centripetal",
    options: [
      "centrifugal",
      "centripetal",
      "buoyant",
      "none of these",
    ]
  },
];